How would you know that he's dead?
I received a photo.
Not some phony mock-up like this one.
A photo of Ko Se-hun, dead.
And do you have the photo?
I don't.
I tore it up and ate it.
Mo Eun.
Do you think this is funny?
What if there might've been
someone else who wanted Ko Se-hun dead?
And maybe they
did what you couldn't to mess with you?
Who else would do
something like that besides you?
What the hell have you done?
Over here.
Ms. An.
- Ah, you're here.
- Hello.
He was found in this freezer, right here.
Interestingly enough,
Ko Se-hun was on trial two years ago.
The victim was?
Yes.
The court kept it sealed
since it was a juvenile case,
and it never made the news
because of COVID.
And this crime's victim?
Both the victim and her father
committed suicide.
I'll see if I can pull anything up
on the rest of the family.
He hasn't said a word.
I mean, he lost his son
and his daughter-in-law.
And now his grandson too?
I'm not surprised.
Sir, I… I, uh…
If you don't mind,
I'd like to leave now.
I'm sure there's something
you can tell us.
Can we please do this later?
By the way,
we've scheduled an autopsy
for this afternoon.
I'll be in touch, sir.
As for the case of the missing boy,
we have tragic news,
as Ko Se-hun, last seen Friday,
was found dead by the authorities
just this afternoon.
This house is the home
of the victim and his two parents,
supposedly vacant
since the couple's murder.
Ko's body was found frozen solid
in a freezer unit in the home's basement.
Police suspect that Ko was confined
and subsequently killed
at this location on Friday evening,
the same day as his disappearance.
Forensic teams are currently sweeping
the crime scene…
Why are you staring at me like that?
…also stated
that in addition to the freezer…
This wasn't
you, right?
…suffered excruciating pain
before his death. While no suspect has…
My doing?
…continue their investigation,
keeping open the possibility…
Never mind.
…to the murder of Ko's parents.
Could Ko's murder be a coincidence,
considering it happened a mere four months
after his parents' death?
This is a truly harrowing tragedy
that has left the public in shock,
but also raises the concerning question…
According to the investigators,
both the brutality in the killing
and how the body was disposed of
would indicate the murder was premeditated
rather than spontaneous.
Further investigation will be required
to determine the exact cause of death.
Police have begun reviewing CCTV footage
and entry logs from the areas
around the crime scene
in an effort to track down
a potential suspect's movements.
Additionally,
an autopsy has been requested
through the National Forensic Service
to try and determine
the exact time of death
and method of murder.
Authorities are conducting
a forensic analysis
of physical evidence recovered…
Mun-jun.
Could you pick up Sop for me
from kindergarten?
And could you please
take her home with you?
Just a couple of days.
I'll explain later.
Meanwhile, a resurfaced interview
with Ko's parents' accused killer, Mo,
is drawing renewed public attention.
Let's revisit that interview.
As I'm sure you know, little boy,
your mom and dad weren't such good people.
Your crime is being their child,
and now you're paying for it too.
Mo's remarks
stirred controversy at the time…
There might have been
someone else who wanted Ko Se-hun dead.
And maybe they
did what you couldn't to mess with you?
Police are focusing their investigation
on uncovering a possible motive
and determining whether or not
the two cases are connected.
The investigative team are also currently
conducting a thorough background inquiry,
including Ko Se-hun's relationship
with his parents.
They are relying on Ko's friends'
and neighbors' testimonies
to help gain insight into his character,
and in doing so,
hopefully understanding the circumstances
that led to his untimely death.
Police continue to review CCTV
and surveillance footage
and communication records
to try and trace his movements
before and after the incident.
Who the hell is it?
Scale.
3.0.
2.5.
3.5.
3.5
This will likely be very distressing, sir.
Sure you wanna watch?
Scalpel.
The cause of death was stab wounds
to the right side of the neck,
piercing the carotid artery
four times in total.
And there are marks that indicate
he was strangled with both hands,
and signs of urinary incontinence.
So he pissed himself?
Then the strangulation
was with intent to kill?
Well, it took him right to the verge.
But it was the stabbing
that killed him, right?
How about the time of death?
The fact that the body
was frozen complicates things,
but he still had hamburger in his stomach,
so I'd say death occurred
within two hours of ingestion.
Okay, thank you.
Mm. Thank you so much.
Sir.
I think it's time I hear from you now.
When you first called it in,
you said something
about him not being able
to return to his old neighborhood.
I don't recall anything like that.
Could it have anything to do with perhaps
when Se-hun was tried in juvenile court?
I don't recall.
That incident drove the victim
and her father to take their own lives.
Were you aware of that?
I don't recall.
Sir.
We really need you to tell us everything
you know about the incident.
That way we can make some--
At that time, my late son and his wife,
we weren't getting along,
so I don't know the details.
I HOPE HE DESERVES TO DIE
I'LL ALWAYS WATCH YOU AND ROOT FOR YOU
WHATEVER YOU DO
There's not much time left.
Don't try and get smart now.
If you don't kill him,
then I'll send someone else.
And if that person should fail,
then I'll just send another.
No matter what…
…that boy
is going to die.
LAWYER JANG JEONG-GU
POOJIM BAKERY & CAFÉ
Mr. Jin did me a favor
and set up the meeting.
I wanted to speak with Mo Eun…
to find out why she tried to kill herself
right before taking the stand.
And then
I saw you there in a doctor's coat,
running off in a panic.
I thought to myself,
"What's she doing here?"
And what's with the doctor's coat?
And where is she rushing off to?
The missing ki… I mean…
The dead kid. You went to his place.
Why? How did you even know?
Is it because you had something
to do with it, Ms. An?
Don't tell me you made
some kind of arrangement with Mo Eun?
I'm expected to be your lawyer, aren't I?
I'm doing the most that I can here.
Just say something
so that I can trust you!
There's something I've always wanted
to ask you, but never have.
Why'd you choose to hire me
to be your lawyer?
It's time for you to go.
Really?
Oh? Oh, yes. That's ours, yeah.
- Thank you.
- What about this?
Your coffee will be out in a moment.
Just a couple hours, okay?
Huh? It's you, Yun-su.
You're even thinner
than the last time I saw you.
- Did you bring Sop with you?
- Did you do it?
Ko Se-hun, the kid?
Were you the one who did it?
I'm not sure what you--
You killed him 'cause Mo Eun asked you to.
I didn't kill anyone.
- Huh?
- Give it!
What are you doing?
Keep still.
The passcode?
I can tell
you're not really close with her.
Don't move a muscle.
I'm not scared of you.
My parents own this place. If I scream,
everyone will come running and find you.
But that's not what I was told to do.
Mo Eun told me just to watch you.
I assume she has something on you too.
Assume?
Yeah, you assume, don't you?
Mo Eun, she's…
she's a good person.
How can you believe her?
Because she saved my life,
and because she was…
and because she was the only one
who ever gave me anything,
and I wasn't just some fat girl to her.
The victim had an older sister.
Her name was Kang So-hae.
But she died a year ago,
somewhere near the Chiang Rai border
in an apparent car fire.
Um, only records we have
show that she moved to Germany
at 17 to study abroad,
where she then graduated
from medical school
and worked
for an international relief org.
She spent her last two years
at a refugee camp in Chiang Rai,
but there is little to no record
of her here in Korea.
Can you reach out to someone
in Chiang Rai directly?
Yeah, I'm on it.
Okay.
PUBLIC DEFENDER'S OFFICE
I can say that, at first,
the whole case seemed clear-cut.
The male student in question
got the female student, the victim, drunk
and then proceeded
to sexually assault her,
but also he secretly filmed it.
That was that.
The evidence was solid.
The accused even admitted it.
But then things began
to change during the trial?
Well, the family of the perpetrator…
Let's just say they had influence.
They called in some friends.
Testimonies began to shift.
Blame was being placed on the girl again,
practically nullifying the case.
Things like, "it wasn't rape,"
or she drank with him willingly,
or she was all over him.
There were some that alleged
that she had worked as an escort.
Is that rumor why Kang So-mang
resorted to suicide?
Well, the rumors were one thing.
While the case was on trial,
the perpetrator, he…
he sent the video
to all the people that she knew.
What he did was basically send it
to every person in her phone contacts.
Please.
Come on, please pick up.
MY SIS♥
I told you
I'd make you pay for this, didn't I?
Did you think
I wouldn't go through with it?
KO SE-HUN
TO: ME, 146 MORE
ONE VIDEO ATTACHMENT
Stop it.
Just stay still. Understand?
And his punishment
was just a probation order?
As a minor, yes, it was.
THE LATE KANG SO-MANG
She's being discharged from the hospital.
You know there's a proper procedure.
Should we take this
to the prosecutor's office, then?
Or just handle it here?
I'm fine with here.
Now… that Ko Se-hun's dead…
how does that make you feel?
I don't know.
"2020 Pu 14, Defendant Ko Se-hun."
"Violation of the Act of Protection
of Children and Youth."
"The Production and Distribution
of Obscene Materials."
"The defendant, Ko Se-hun,
is charged with recording a video
of the victim engaging in sexual activity
and subsequently sharing
and distributing the material
with all individuals
in the victim's phone contact list."
You show no emotion at that,
like you don't know what I'm saying.
So if he sent it to every person
on that contact list, well, then,
I suppose her father must've seen it
and her older sister too.
She must've been devastated.
That's a reason to commit suicide.
And because he wasn't able
to protect his daughter,
the father made the same decision.
Her sister died around then as well.
Apparently, a car accident in Thailand.
Damn.
What a tragic story.
Yeah.
Here's a detail you haven't heard before.
This is a statement from "P,"
a colleague of the victim.
"The victim had shown interest
in the defendant."
"I personally witnessed
excessive physical contact
between them at a drinking party."
"Additionally, the victim, Kang So-mang,
shared her own experience
working as an escort
and encouraged it."
"The court recognizes
the statements of 'P' and others
around the two at the time."
"Because of these statements,
we cannot conclude the assault occurred
as a result of coercion."
"Rather, it is considered reasonable
to find credibility
in the defendant's claim
that the intercourse
took place with the understanding
of mutual consent."
Kang So-Mang's sister, Kang So-hae.
Can you imagine how much rage
she would be feeling?
Thoughts of revenge
would consume her completely,
and people must've thought
she was a psychopath.
That's why no one
could find any indication
of a grudge between her and her victims.
You beat the polygraph
because the answers you provided
to the baseline questions were made up,
skewing the reports.
Is your name Mo Eun?
Yes.
Kang So-hae is alive and well.
That woman who died in Thailand,
that was someone else.
I wonder how that sad woman
ended up dead in a car.
What are you…
What are you trying to imply?
You couldn't stand it, could you?
That the boy was still alive.
That's why you put An Yun-su up to it.
That's why you made the deal.
Again,
you returned to An Yun-su, didn't you?
You didn't kill him.
Lee Ki-dae was not you.
You spent years doing
medical volunteer work in a refugee camp.
You were working to preserve lives,
not to end them.
That's Kang So-hae's pure nature.
She'd never be able to kill someone
for whom she didn't bear a grudge.
DETECTIVE RYU JI-SU
Yeah. I'm listening.
Sir, we got the results
on the hair collected at the scene.
It's a match for An Yun-su.
Okay. Thank you.
Was the revenge worth it?
An Yun-su is now a killer again.
Only this time, you did it to her.
Can I go now?
Oh.
An Yun-su.
She didn't kill Ko Se-hun.
That's her pure nature.
GANGAN DAILY
Yeah, Hong Se-young speaking.
I'm calling because I have
some information about Ko Se-hun.
You know, the murder victim.
Oh, okay. Can you please hold?
Okay. Tell me what's the nature
of the info you have?
There's a connection.
A connection between Mo Eun,
the Witch, and Ko Se-hun's past crime.
Oh, I'm sorry, uh, but may I be so forward
as to ask who is calling?
Just list me
as an anonymous tipster, please.
Ah.
Okay, please continue.
This is a statement from "P,"
a colleague of the victim.
"The victim had shown interest
in the defendant."
"Additionally, the victim, Kang So-mang,
shared her own experience
working as an escort and encouraged it."
KO SE-HUN'S JUVENILE COURT RECORD REVEALED
INVESTIGATION PROBING
POTENTIAL REVENGE MOTIVE
Wait here.
Inmate 407.
Wait here for a bit, then head back
with the others after visitation.
Shit. See ya.
Thankfully, the authorities were able to…
Hey! How'd the meeting
with your boyfriend go, you little slut?
He's my friend. That's it.
The only guys who show up
at a women's prison
are boyfriends
or people looking for money.
The injuries have been
confirmed as non-life-threatening.
However, prospective residents…
Hospital food that bad? Look at you.
You're back already.
Ooh.
…and are planning collective action.
The Ministry of Land has stated that…
How come you two bitches
didn't pitch in again?
Nobody out there cares enough
about you to throw some money your way?
God.
All right.
Snacks on me today. Eat up, ladies!
Hey! You two fighting or something?
What's going on?
Ah, settle it after you eat.
The juvenile
court records of the late Ko Se-hun
have been made public.
The details of the records have triggered
a new round of intense investigation
into the cause
and circumstances of his death.
Police are closely analyzing…
What you said to me before.
Can you say it again?
…some connection to his prior offenses
and his death.
Namely, the possibility
that there may have been…
You said something
about divine punishment.
They may have connections to Ko's past…
I'm pretty sure that's what you said.
You know,
I actually knew the people you killed.
Honestly…
I think what they got
was divine punishment.
You're "P," aren't you?
It has been confirmed that Mo,
the suspect in
the Ilsan dentist couple murder case,
assumed a false identity.
According to investigators,
the suspect's real surname is Kang.
Records show that Kang was selected
as a government-sponsored overseas student
at 17 and graduated
from medical school in Germany…
- Let's go.
- Stop it! What are you doing? Stop it!
Hey, hey, hey! Hey, take it easy!
That's why I told you
I don't like kids her age.
Police are focusing their investigation
on her motive and related connections
in an effort to uncover
the full truth behind this case,
including the forgery of her identity
and her complex family background.
An Yun-su is making her way back home
from the bakery now.
She doesn't seem aware
that we have evidence against her yet.
- We'll conduct the arrest at her place.
- Sir, afternoon.
And her probation officer? Where is she?
She's on her way here right now.
As requested, here is her movement log
for the day Ko Se-hun was killed.
I don't see any record of her going
anywhere near the crime scene.
These lines just show a path
between her home and the kindergarten.
- Sorry, I'm late. Hello.
- There you are.
Show me all the records.
I want a complete history.
Go ahead and pull up her full movement log
since the time of her release.
Got it.
- Over there. Zoom in on that.
- Okay.
It looks like she followed this path
on the 1st and the 3rd,
and also on the 4th and 6th.
That would follow Ko Se-hun's movements.
She must've been following him
because she needed to plot the kill.
An Yun-su's log
on that day.
Can you confirm it?
Uh, ah…
Well, she called me at, uh, 7:00 p.m.
with a complaint
that her ankle monitor
had broken in a fall,
so I went to her place
about an hour later to replace it.
Wait. So,
you didn't think to tell us?
Well, I thought it's not possible.
I mean, it was raining heavily,
and considering the travel time.
- I assumed she couldn't do it in an hour.
- Why would you assume something like that?
Sop keeps saying she misses you,
so we're on our way there now.
Yun-su just got home.
Keep things calm.
Try and handle the arrest quietly.
Affirmative.
Oh.
Hi.
You know who I am, don't you?
Someone sent this to me.
But don't be scared.
I just want to hear you tell me the truth.
Come in.
Can I offer you tea?
No, thank you.
I think I'm gonna have some.
One day,
I was told my son
and his wife had been murdered.
I spent every waking day as a soldier,
and I never spoke kindly
of my son his whole life.
Even when he died,
I couldn't shed a single tear.
Yesterday, however,
I saw my grandson dead with my own eyes.
Inside a cold freezer.
I knew that I simply couldn't die
without knowing…
I couldn't die without knowing why!
And I intend to find out!
Get back here! Stop!
Whoa, who drives like…
Uh, wasn't that An Yun-su's car?
- Well, go on. Follow it.
- Sir.
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
NIGHT CURFEW VIOLATION
Notify all police
of An Yun-su's location now.
RETURN TO YOUR DESIGNATED AREA IMMEDIATELY
CONTACT YOUR SUPERVISOR
TO CONFIRM THE VIOLATION
PROBATION OFFICER BAE SUN-DEOK
…you are trying to reach is unavailable.
You'll be directed to voicemail.
Come on. Come on.
The phone you are trying to reach
has been powered off.
You'll be directed to voicemail.
HAIR FOUND AT KO'S MURDER SCENE
IDENTIFIED AS TEACHER A'S
An Yun-su is at Haneul Mart
in Jungang-dong.
- Try to intercept her there.
- Copy.
Come on. Hurry. Come on. Come on.
ELECTRONIC MONITORING SIGNAL LOST
A spike in stress was just doing a number
on her circulation.
I appreciate it.
You won't have a run-in with her
as long as I'm here.
I promise you that much at least.
We've moved her
to a solitary cell on the first floor,
so you'll be fine.
There's no need to be scared.
In fact, I think there's no safer place.
NEW REVELATIONS IN KO'S MURDER CASE
DEAL BETWEEN THE WITCH AND AN DISCOVERED
Doctor, do you mind turning off the TV?
Oh, sure.
TAILED KO SE-HUN
REMOVED ANKLE TAG BEFORE MURDER
I'll follow you guys, okay?
Back to the cell block?
- I have to administer some insulin.
- Okay.
And remember, if you're anxious
or have any trouble breathing,
just ask to come back to the infirmary.
Here's my stop. Good night.
Put it away. Put it away. Quiet!
What's going on?
Shit, busted.
7137, get out here.
You wanna explain?
So sorry, ma'am.
How many times do I have to warn you?
All right.
Eating is prohibited after dark.
Ms. Eom, uh, what's she doing?
Stop!
Oh God!
Oh no!
No!